

# PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

HTML CSS

JavaScript

Ruby

Rails SEO

React

WordPress

Social media

Right to work in Australia

#### PERSONAL SKILLS

Reliable and professional Organized Time management Team player Fast learner Motivated

### CONTACT

0421367414

jjpalco@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/joseparraalcolea/ github.com/JoseParraA www.tiempodexplorar.com

#### SOCIAL

@ParraAlcolea

# JOSE PARRA ALCOLEA

## WEB DEVELOPER

#### **ABOUT**

I left Spain in 2013 in search of new professional opportunities and the experience of living abroad. Designing and building my own travel blog is when I realised that I really enjoyed programming. I have been exploring the world of web development more seriously since 2017 via online courses with Codeacademy, Udacity and most recently the Web Development Immersive at General Assembly.

My experiences throughout my life have taught me how important it is to have a fulfilling career and to constantly be learning. I have definitely found my passion in Web Development and would love to join a company who are creative and results driven!

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### CONSTRUCTION

Fusion | Jan 2017 - Jan 2018

• Working 7-3 allows me to study code in the afternoon.

#### STOCKROOM LEADER AND ASSISTANT

Inditex | Nov 2014 - Dec 2016

- Organising the product and staff to complete the work in the most efficient way according to the plan.
- Managing the stockroom in a planned, organised and strategic manner.

#### **CO-FOUNDER**

Tiempo de explorar travel blog | Apr 2012 - Present

- · Planning and developing the digital media strategy
- Implementing SEO strategies
- Promoting the blog using social media platforms and email marketing
- Writing articles related to travelling

#### OFFICE MANAGER

Palco | Nov 2009 - Oct 2013

- Examining bank statements and reconciling them with general ledger entries
  - Examining expenses submitted by employees
- Managing the stockroom in a planned, organised and strategic manner.

#### **EDUCATION**

- WEB DEVELOPER IMMERSIVE AT GENERAL ASSEMBLY (MAY 2018)
- BACHELOR DEGREE IN BUSINESS ADMINISTRATION. UNIVERSITY OF ALMERIA.
- ENGLISH (ADVANCE)
- SPANISH (NATIVE)